Guide to the Washington State University Capital Planning Building Files 1957-1998
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- University Facilities Planning and Student Housing Research - Qualifications Submittal Document. 1/1995. / MGT of America, Inc. (Box 29)
- The University of Connecticut Residential Life Facilities Study - Summary Report. 1/1991. / Division of Student Affairs and Services; Dober, Lidsky, Craig and Associates, Inc. (Box 29)
- Proposed Undergraduate Housing Facility Program - Babson College. Babson College 1991 New Housing Study Committee. 3/1991. / Dober, Lidsky, Craig and Associates, Inc., Consultants (Box 29)
- Student Housing Proposal/Statement of Qualifications. 1/1995. / IBI Group - Architects and Engineers (Box 29)
- Graduate Student Housing - Massachusetts Institute of Technology/ 143 Albany Street. 5/1988. / Facility Program Dober and Associates, Incorporated Planning Consultants (Box 29)
- Plant Growth Wheat Research Facility - Summary of Field and laboratory Test Results. 8/1997. / File: WASUNI - M9602A Contract: 12380; Strata Geotechnical Engineering and Materials Testing (Box 29)
- Incinerator - Replacement Medical Waste Incinerator - Environmental Impact Statement Volume I of II WSU. 10/1996. (Box 29)
- Incinerator - Replacement Medical Waste Incinerator - Environmental Impact Statement Volume II of II WSU. 10/1996. (Box 29)
- Incinerator - Design Development Submittal for Incinerator Project. Civil Design Analysis/Preliminary Structural Calculations/Mechanical/Electrical. 7/1997. / Bovay Northwest (Box 29)
- Incinerator - Design Development Submittal for Incinerator Project. 7/1997. / Bovay Northwest (Box 30)
- Incinerator - New Incineration Facility/Wastewater Pre-Treatment Study. 2/1997. / Bovay Northwest (Box 30)
- Incinerator - Engineering Report Chapter 6 Site Selection. 7/1993. / Bovay Northwest (Box 30)
- Waste Management Evaluations - Proposal for Consulting Services. 2/1990. / Doucet and Mainka, P.C. (Box 30)
- Incinerator - Multicare Medical Center Incineration Project. Final Environmental Impact Statement. Pursuant to the State Environmental Policy Act of 1984 Chapter 43.2 (RCW 2/1990). (Box 30)
- Waste Management Program Evaluation - Technical and Economic Feasibility Report. 2/1990. / Doucet and Mainka, P.C. (Box 30)
- Final Waste Management Program Evaluation - Report (DM347). 5/1990. / Doucet and Mainka, P.C. (Box 30)
- Yakama Village - One - Year Warranty Inspection Final Report Checklist. 1/1997. / Design West (Box 30)
- Student Services Addition - Mechanical Fixture Information Booklet. 9/1993. / Mahlum and Nordfors Mckinley Gordon (Box 30)
- Student Services Addition - Design Development Phase - Schematic Design Review Comments. 3/1993. / McKinley Gordon - A Professional Service Corporation (Box 30)
- French Administration Building Addition - Proposal to provide Value Engineering Services. 6/1993. / Presented to: Mahlum and Nordfors Mckinley Gordon; Submitted by: KJM and Associates, LTD (Box 30)
- Student Services Addition Design Development Estimate - Draft. 10/1993. / Turner Construction Company (Box 30)
- Student Services Addition - Electrical Fixture Information Booklet. 9/1993. / Mahlum and Nordfors Mckinley Gordon (Box 30)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Design Development Supplemental Information: Estimate of Construction Cost; Program Area Comparison; Architectural Details; Structural Notes; Mechanical Narrative; Light Fixture Schedule. 11/1994. / Cardwell/Thomas and Associates/Arc (Box 30)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Schematic Design. 6/1994. / Cardwell/Thomas and Associates/Architects (Box 30)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Selected Product Information. Division 8 Doors and Windows/Division 9 Finishes/Division 10 Specialties. 3/1995. / Cardwell/Thomas and Associates/Architects (Box 30)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Addenda 1 - 6 Bid Package II. 5/1998. / Cardwell/Thomas and Associates (Box 30)
- Thompson Hall - Hazardous Material Survey - Addendum No. 1. 10/1997. / SCM Consultants Inc. (Box 30)
- Thompson Hall Renewal - Value Engineering Study. 10/1994. / Olympic Associates Company (Box 30)
- Thompson Hall Hazardous Materials Survey Project 3710.010. 2/1995. / SCM Consultants, Inc. - Architects and Engineers (Box 30)
- Thompson Hall Renewal Project - Value Engineering Services. 7/1994. / Cardwell/Thomas and Associates (Box 30)
- Todd Hall - Health and Safety Observations. 9/1994. / AGRA Earth and Environment, Inc. (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Renewal - Copy Finish Hardware Schedule for your review and comment. 3/1994. / The Henry Klein Partnership (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Renewal - Value Engineering Study. 10/1992. / The Henry Klein Partnership (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Renovation - Schematic Drawings. 7/1990. / The Henry Klein Partnership; Structural: ABJKMechanical: Halvorson, Beach and Bower; Electrical: Sparling and Assoc., Inc. (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Renovation - Room Capacity Chart along with drawings. 10/1991. / The Henry Klein Partnership (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Renovation - Health and Safety Plan - Demolition of Lead Paint Containing Material R14. 3/1994. / AGRA - Engineering and Environmental Services (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Renewal - Allotment Request for Construction - Renovation - renovation will bring fire, safety, and handicapped compliance up to date. 12/1993. (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Addition - Construction Cost Estimate. 1/1989. / Olympic Associates Company (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Addition - Foundation Investigation. 7/1984. / c/o Henry Klein Partnership; Shannon and Wilson, Inc. (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Addition - Fire Alarm and Clock Control System. 12/1989. / Simplex (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Addition - C.D. Contractors, Inc. Certified Payroll Reports beginning with period ending 6/23/1989 to date. 11/1989. / C and D General Contractors. (Box 30)
- Todd Hall Addition - Equipment Brochures Job # 3147. 12/1988. / FORMA - Interior Design Planning and Purchasing (Box 31)
- Consolidated Information Center (C.I.C.) - Design Development Outline Specifications. 12/1994. / Integrus Architecture (Box 31)
- Consolidated Information Center - Drainage Report (Tri-Cities). 12/1994. / Rose Water Engineering, Inc. (Box 31)
- Consolidated Information Center - Energy Conservation Report (Tri-Cities). 1/1995. / MW Consulting Engineers (Box 31)
- Consolidated Information Center - Value Engineering Study - Tri-Cities Branch. 11/1994. / Roen Associates (Box 31)
- Hazardous Communication - Hazardous Chemical Program Manual. 7/1989. / Contractors Northwest; Inc. (Box 31)
- Consolidated Information Center - Design Development Cost Estimate (Tri-Cities). 1/1995. (Box 31)
- Consolidated Information Center Preliminary Program Information. 12/1993. / Integrus Architecture, P.S. (Box 31)
- Tri-Cities WSU - Campus Expansion Traffic Impact Study - Level of Service Reports - Existing Condition Year Traffix System Version 6.7. 1994. / Licensed To INCA Engineers, Inc. (Box 31)
- Tri-Cities Campus Expansion - Traffic Impact Study. 8/1994. / Prepared by INCA Engineers, Inc. (Box 31)
- Consolidated Information Center - Phase I Geotechnical Studies. 12/1994. / Shannon and Wilson, Inc. - Geotechnical and Environmental Consultants (Box 31)
- Center for Northwest Anthropology - A Cultural Resources Survey of the WSU Tri-Cities Branch Campus Properties Contributions in Cultural Resource Management No. 49. 2/1995. (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Phase 11 Building Construction - Quality Control Program. / Morgen and Oswood Construction Co., Inc. (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Site Preparation Phase I - Information for Preparation of Bids on Excavation and Fill. (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Phase II: Building Construction Contract No. 11470. Environmental and Pollution Prevention Plan. / Morgen and Oswood Construction Co., Inc (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Project Information and Procedures. Owners Project # 11470. / Morgen and Oswood Project Number 9304 (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Value Engineering and Constructability Study. 5/1992. / Morrison Knudsen Corporation (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Project Manual for Phase I: Site Grading/ Job Number 5-88-328A. 6/1991. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates Architects and Planners (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Clinic Building - Environmental Analysis. Volume Five of Six Oregon State University Environmental Quality Study (Item 10.10). Submitted to Grants and Contracts Management Branch - Public Health Service. / Submitted by Mr. Mil (Box 31)
- Environmental Quality Study for (Exhibit D). Veterinary Research Laboratory Addition, Moscow Idaho. Caldwell Veterinary Medical Center, Caldwell, Idaho. Caldwell Veterinary Medical Center Isolation Building. Caldwell, Idaho. Volume Six of Six - University (Box 31)
- College of Veterinary Medicine Capital Budget Request - Construction of New Veterinary Teaching Hospital. 1989 -1999. (Box 31)
- McCoy /Bustad Complex - Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Site Study. 4/1988. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates - Architects and Planners (Box 31)
- New Veterinary Teaching Hospital - College of Veterinary Medicine - Schematic Design. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates - Architects and Planners; Thomas J. Gerard and Associates, Inc. - MechanicalSuden, Golden and Guest, Inc. - Structural; Foil - Wyatt - Mc (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - A Report on Site Planning. 11/1988. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture - Campus Planners (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital - Interview. 10/1987. / Project Design Team: De Neff Deeble Barton Associates Architects and Planners; Foil - Wyatt - McKewen - Veterinary Planning ConsultantSuden, Golden and Guest, Inc. - Structural Engineers; Thorson Partners (Box 31)
- Veterinary Hospital - Benefit and Life Cycle Cost Analysis Summary. (Box 31)
- Veterinary Teaching Hospital Complex - Review Copy of Program. 7/1988. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates - Architects and Planners; Program Consultant: Foil - Wyatt - Mckewen (Box 32)
- New Veterinary Teaching Hospital - College of Veterinary Medicine. 12/1990. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates Program consultant - Foil - Wyatt - Mckewen (Box 32)
- New Veterinary Teaching Hospital Complex Program (Needs Not Meet In New Construction). 12/1990. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates Foil - Wyatt - Mckewen (Box 32)
- Health Professions Educational Facilities Construction Grant - Volume One of Six. 7/1977. / Submitted by: Washington State University, Oregon State University, University of Idaho (Box 32)